saclaw.org 2019-02-11

# Privacy Policy | saclaw.org

This privacy policy describes how the Sacramento County Public Law Library uses personal information collected at this site. Please read this policy carefully before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using this site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. Websites you link to from [www.saclaw.org](https://saclaw.org/) may have privacy provisions that differ from those of the library’s website.

SCPLL collects non-identifying information to improve the functionality, content, and performance of the library’s website. When you visit www.saclaw.org, we collect information regarding:

  * Your Internet location (IP address)
  * The pages you visit on our website
  * The web page from which you came to our site
  * The software you use to visit our site

The library does not:

  * Collect personally identifiable information unless you voluntarily provide it to us
  * Provide or sell any information to outside agencies

* * *

**Contact Us**  
We use email addresses to answer email we receive on our Contact Us form. These addresses are not used for any other purpose, and are not shared with outside parties.

**Listserv**  
If you wish to receive email notices about library news and upcoming events, you may register for our email listserv. The library’s listserv is hosted by Constant Contact, a marketing cloud service. Email addresses provided for this purpose are not used in other ways, nor are they shared with third parties other than our listserv host. Please see the [Constant Contact Privacy Policy](https://www.constantcontact.com/legal/privacy-statement) for more details.

**MCLE Registrations**  
When registering online for our classes, you will be required to provide personally identifying information, including your name, address, and credit card information. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to process your class registration and marketing for future MCLE Classes.

**Online Payments**  
We collect information about you during the checkout process on our online store. When you purchase from us, we’ll ask you to provide information including your name, billing address, shipping address, email address, phone number, credit card/payment details and optional account information like username and password. We’ll use this information for purposes, such as, to:  
• Send you information about your account and order  
• Respond to your requests, including refunds and complaints  
• Process payments and prevent fraud  
• Set up your account for our store  
• Comply with any legal obligations we have, such as calculating taxes  
• Improve our store offerings  
• Send you marketing messages, if you choose to receive them  
If you create an account, we will store your name, address, email and phone number, which will be used to populate the checkout for future orders. We generally store information about you for as long as we need the information for the purposes for which we collect and use it, and we are not legally required to continue to keep it. We’ll also use cookies to keep track of cart contents while you’re browsing our site.

We accept payments through PayPal. When processing payments, some of your data will be passed to PayPal, including information required to process or support the payment, such as the purchase total and billing information. Please see the [PayPal Privacy Policy](https://www.paypal.com/us/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full) for more details.

**Online Donations**  
We accept donation payments through PayPal. When processing donations, some of your data will be passed to PayPal, including information required to process or support the payment, such as the billing information. Please see the [PayPal Privacy Policy](https://www.paypal.com/us/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full) for more details.

**Contact Information**  
If you have any questions, concerns or comments about out privacy policy, you may contact us [via email](https://saclaw.org/contact/ "Contact") or 916-874-6011.
